<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prajwal Nayak</title>
    <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prajwal Nayak</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Consistently evolving the snapshots of perception. Thoughts / suggestions / feedback welcome at HERE. Thank you for reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jog Falls</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/jogfalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/jogfalls/</guid>
      <description>Breathtaking! A stare at the water falling from 100s of feet above the ground, gives an illusion of heaven. The milk-ish water molecules racing to hit the ground is a mesmerizing view. Sitting on the rocks and just staring at them for hours brings tranquility. It makes one realize what true beauty is, how insignificant one is at the face of a larger creation.
By observing the crowd, It seemed like everybody is into modeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WKC Camps</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/wkccamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 21:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/wkccamp/</guid>
      <description>In 2015, a tyro entered the WORLD KONKANI CENTER with no idea whatsoever. Analogous to a stone, without an identity or pride towards where it came from. My understanding and perspective were limited to a few people and a small geographic area. I was a nice and nerdy person. But, I had to buck up, I had to work in the right direction to let my inner talents sprout. It is an undeniable fact that WKC became a catalyst in the transformation and rejuvenation of my naive personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MIT Manipal</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/mitmanipal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 21:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/mitmanipal/</guid>
      <description>Soon after a hectic year of study and entrance exams, came a year with power packed experiences. I could recall from my memory, an unexpected incidence. A year ago I, while returning to my home, from temple, lost my way and ended up in the crowded Manipal Campus. At that moment I saw myself to be there as a student. Destiny aligned with my interests, got admission in one of the best college, in my favorite branch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 21:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/college/</guid>
      <description>Life at college is the time when the teenage years end and we all dive deep into the ocean of new beginnings and possibilities. The diamond jubilee year for Manipal Institute of Technology, and my second year of engineering started after a long summer vacations of about two and a half months, in the rainy month of august. The year that welcomed engineering undergrads to their respective branches. It was that time when a student gets the feeling of being a ‘senior’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Software Engineer by profession and hustler by choice. Rightenousness and compassionate capitalism are the principles I believe in.
Leverage of Software technology and the possibility of a resource unconstrained future excites me.
Wanna grab a cup of coffee ☕ ? or have a small chat 🤝🏻, feel free to ping me HERE. Thanks for Visiting !! 👍🏻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m available at prajwalnayak7@gmail.com and +919740662196.
Click to View My Resume
Click here to Connect via LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
