<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prajwal Nayak</title>
    <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prajwal Nayak</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/project/</guid>
      <description>GitHub - Open Source Projects
 Caching / Notifications - CFTR
 Led the implementation of caching across the application. Owner of notifications. Revamped the code for robustness and reduced code size by ~50%. Python best practices in package management, git pre-commit autiomatic static checks.
 MySQL - Redis - Elasticsearch - hooks - Bash shell - Profiling  WhatsApp Communication
 Instant Payouts / small loans for MSMEs.
Weekly sales report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Consistently evolving the snapshots of perception. Thoughts / suggestions / feedback welcome at HERE. Thank you for reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jog Falls</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/jogfalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/jogfalls/</guid>
      <description>🌐
Breathtaking! A stare at the water falling from 100s of feet above the ground, gives an illusion of heaven. The milk-ish water molecules racing to hit the ground is a mesmerizing view. Sitting on the rocks and just staring at them for hours brings tranquility. It makes one realize what true beauty is, how insignificant one is at the face of a larger creation.
By observing the crowd, It seemed like everybody is into modeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under-graduate</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 21:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/college/</guid>
      <description>Soon after a hectic year of study and exams, began a year with power-packed experiences. I could recall a fortuitous incidence. A year ago I, while returning to my home, from the Venugopal temple, lost my way and ended up in the crowded Manipal Campus. At that moment I saw myself to be a student there in the distant hypothetical future. Destiny aligned with my interests, received admission there, in my favorite branch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Software Engineer by profession and hustler by choice. Rightenousness and compassionate capitalism are the principles I believe in.
Leverage of technology and the possibility of a resource unconstrained future excites me.
Wanna grab a cup of coffee ☕ ? or have a small chat 🤝🏻, feel free to ping me HERE. Thanks for Visiting !! 👍🏻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m available at prajwalnayak7@gmail.com and +919740662196.
Click to View My Resume / CV
Click here to Connect via LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
