<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>education on Prajwal Nayak</title>
    <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in education on Prajwal Nayak</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 21:56:53 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WKC Camps</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/wkccamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 21:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/wkccamp/</guid>
      <description>In 2015, a tyro entered the WORLD KONKANI CENTER with no idea whatsoever. Analogous to a stone, without an identity or pride towards where it came from. My understanding and perspective were limited to a few people and a small geographic area. I was a nice and nerdy person. But, I had to buck up, I had to work in the right direction to let my inner talents sprout. It is an undeniable fact that WKC became a catalyst in the transformation and rejuvenation of my naive personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MIT Manipal</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/mitmanipal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 21:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/mitmanipal/</guid>
      <description>Soon after a hectic year of study and entrance exams, came a year with power packed experiences. I could recall from my memory, an unexpected incidence. A year ago I, while returning to my home, from temple, lost my way and ended up in the crowded Manipal Campus. At that moment I saw myself to be there as a student. Destiny aligned with my interests, got admission in one of the best college, in my favorite branch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate</title>
      <link>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 21:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prajwalnayak7.github.io/college/</guid>
      <description>Life at college is the time when the teenage years end and we all dive deep into the ocean of new beginnings and possibilities. The diamond jubilee year for Manipal Institute of Technology, and my second year of engineering started after a long summer vacations of about two and a half months, in the rainy month of august. The year that welcomed engineering undergrads to their respective branches. It was that time when a student gets the feeling of being a ‘senior’.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
